Guide to the Toba Pato Tucker Photographs and Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Re Viewing the American Landscape West & Southwest, 2012-2015; Series V; (29 boxes)
  - Portfolio #1
    - Reference Inkjet Prints, 8.5 inches by 11 inches
      - Photographs in Colorado by William Henry Jackson
        - Garden of the Gods - Colorado Springs
          - Balanced Rock, Garden of the Gods (No. 602), printed 2012; image created circa 1879-1894 (Box 261, Folder 3624)
        - Monument Park - El Paso County
          - Monument Park (No. 1174), printed 2012; image created circa 1885 (Box 261, Folder 3625)
            Original print in Mammoth Plate Photographs of the North American West, Call number WA Photos Folio 1. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 2198-2226.
          - Castleated Rocks near Monument Park (No. 1020?), printed 2012; image created circa 1874 (Box 261, Folder 3626)
            Source of print not located; likely from a digital surrogate in the Digital Collections of Denver Public Library. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 2198-2226.
          - Monument Park (No. 105), printed 2012; image created circa 1874 (Box 261, Folder 3627)
            William Henry Holmes in image. Source of print not located; likely from a digital surrogate in the Digital Collections of Denver Public Library. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 2198-2226.
          - Monument Park (No. 114), printed 2012; image created circa 1874 (Box 261, Folder 3628)
        - Hovenweep, Utah-Colorado Border west of Cortez, Colorado
          - Ruined fortress on the Hovenweep, Utah (No. 172), printed 2012; image created circa 1871-1880 (Box 261, Folder 3629)
            From a digital surrogate in the Digital Collections of Denver Public Library. From William Henry Jackson folio IV. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 2806-2871.
          - Ruined fortress on the Hovenweep, Utah (No. 169), printed 2012; image created circa 1871-1880 (Box 261, Folder 3630)
            Source of print not located; likely from a digital surrogate in the Digital Collections of Denver Public Library. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 2806-2871.
  - Portfolio #2
    Portfolio of exhibition prints by Tucker of sites in Arizona and New Mexico, 2012-2013, as well as reference prints of work by photographers during the nineteenth century including John K. Hillers, William Henry Jackson, and Timothy H. O'Sullivan.
    Organized under two headings: Inkjet prints, 17 inches by 22 inches, and Reference Inkjet Prints, 8.5 inches by 11 inches.
    - Inkjet prints, 17 inches by 22 inches
      Organized by the photographer under ten headings: Canyon de Chelly, Arizona; Grand Canyon, Arizona; Anasazi Ruins - Chaco Canyon, New Mexico; El Morro National Monument, New Mexico; Painted Desert, New Mexico; Petrified Forest, Arizona; Anasazi Ruins - Pueblo of Wupatki, Arizona; Walnut Canyon, Arizona; Sunset Crater, Arizona; and Meteor Crater, also known as Barringer Crater, Arizona, then by sites she visited sequentially at these broader locations. The last folder in this group of material includes original interleaving sheets created by Tucker.
      - Canyon de Chelly, Arizona
        Photographs of Canyon de Chelly National Monument, Arizona.
        - From Rim Drive (No. 2927), 2012 (Box 262 (Oversize), Folder 3631)
        - Untitled (No. 2943), 2012 (Box 262 (Oversize), Folder 3632)
        - Untitled (No. 2947), 2012 (Box 262 (Oversize), Folder 3633)
        - Untitled (No. 2948), 2012 (Box 262 (Oversize), Folder 3634)
        - Petroglyphs (No. 2949), 2012 (Box 262 (Oversize), Folder 3635)
        - Petroglyphs (No. 2954), 2012 (Box 262 (Oversize), Folder 3636)
        - Untitled (No. 2957), 2012 (Box 262 (Oversize), Folder 3637)
        - Untitled (No. 2960), 2012 (Box 262 (Oversize), Folder 3638)
        - Untitled (No. 2966), 2012 (Box 262 (Oversize), Folder 3639)
        - First Ruins (No. 2971), 2012 (Box 262 (Oversize), Folder 3640)
        - Junction Ruins (No. 2978), 2012 (Box 262 (Oversize), Folder 3641)
        - White House Ruins (No. 3017), 2012 (Box 262 (Oversize), Folder 3642)
        - White House Ruins (No. 3021), 2012 (Box 262 (Oversize), Folder 3643)
        - White House Ruins (No. 3022), 2012 (Box 262 (Oversize), Folder 3644)
        - Sliding House Ruins (crevice in rock on right) (No. 3043), 2012 (Box 262 (Oversize), Folder 3645)
        - Hoof Rock (No. 3059), 2012 (Box 262 (Oversize), Folder 3646)
        - Window Rock (No. 3064), 2012 (Box 262 (Oversize), Folder 3647)
        - Window Rock (No. 3082), 2012 (Box 262 (Oversize), Folder 3648)
        - Untitled (No. 3091), 2012 (Box 262 (Oversize), Folder 3649)
        - Spider Woman Rock, from Rim Drive (No. 3121), 2012 (Box 262 (Oversize), Folder 3650)
      - Grand Canyon, Arizona
        - Colorado River, Hance Rapids from Navajo Point (No. 3129), 2012 (Box 263 (Oversize), Folder 3651)
        - Colorado River, Hance Rapids from Navajo Point (No. 3132), 2012 (Box 263 (Oversize), Folder 3652)
        - Grand View Point, A Photographer (No. 3171), 2012 (Box 263 (Oversize), Folder 3653)
        - Bright Angel Trail, right, Rim Lodges, top right (No. 3200), 2012 (Box 263 (Oversize), Folder 3654)
        - The Bright Angel Trail, right (No. 3217), 2012 (Box 263 (Oversize), Folder 3655)
        - The Bright Angel Trail (No. 3221), 2012 (Box 263 (Oversize), Folder 3656)
        - The Bright Angel Trail (No. 3223), 2012 (Box 263 (Oversize), Folder 3657)
        - Enroute to Hermit's Rest (No. 3243), 2012 (Box 263 (Oversize), Folder 3658)
        - Colorado River from Hopi Point (No. 3275), 2012 (Box 263 (Oversize), Folder 3659)
        - Hopi Point (No. 3284), 2012 (Box 263 (Oversize), Folder 3660)
        - Hopi Point (No. 3299), 2012 (Box 263 (Oversize), Folder 3661)
        - Colorado River, Hance Rapids from Mohave Point (No. 3317), 2012 (Box 263 (Oversize), Folder 3662)
        - Colorado River, Hance Rapids from Mohave Point (No. 3326), 2012 (Box 263 (Oversize), Folder 3663)
        - Colorado River, Hance Rapids from Mohave Point (No. 3329), 2012 (Box 263 (Oversize), Folder 3664)
        - Colorado River from Mohave Point (No. 3344), 2012 (Box 263 (Oversize), Folder 3665)
        - Colorado River, Hance Rapids from Mohave Point (No. 3350), 2012 (Box 263 (Oversize), Folder 3666)
        - Colorado River from Mohave Point (No. 3352), 2012 (Box 263 (Oversize), Folder 3667)
        - Colorado River from Pima Point (No. 3376), 2012 (Box 264 (Oversize), Folder 3668)
        - Colorado River from Pima Point (No. 3377), 2012 (Box 264 (Oversize), Folder 3669)
        - Colorado River from Pima Point (No. 3379), 2012 (Box 264 (Oversize), Folder 3670)
        - Colorado River from Pima Point (No. 3384), 2012 (Box 264 (Oversize), Folder 3671)
        - The Bright Angel Trail, from the Trailhead (No. 3398), 2012 (Box 264 (Oversize), Folder 3672)
        - The Bright Angel Trail, Sunrise (No. 3422), 2012 (Box 264 (Oversize), Folder 3673)
        - The Bright Angel Trail, Sunrise - Rim Lodges, top right (No. 3423), 2012 (Box 264 (Oversize), Folder 3674)
        - From Rim at Mather Point, Sunrise (No. 3437), 2012 (Box 264 (Oversize), Folder 3675)
        - From Rim at Mather Point, Sunrise (No. 3446), 2012 (Box 264 (Oversize), Folder 3676)
        - From Rim at Mather Point, Morning (No. 3449), 2012 (Box 264 (Oversize), Folder 3677)
        - From Rim at Mather Point, Morning (No. 3458), 2012 (Box 264 (Oversize), Folder 3678)
        - From Rim at Mather Point, Morning (No. 3461), 2012 (Box 264 (Oversize), Folder 3679)
        - From Rim at Mather Point, Morning (No. 3464), 2012 (Box 264 (Oversize), Folder 3680)
        - Colorado River From Mather Point (No. 3486), 2012 (Box 264 (Oversize), Folder 3681)
      - Anasazi Ruins - Chaco Canyon, New Mexico
        - Chetro Ketl Ancestral Pueblo (No. 3587), 2012 (Box 265 (Oversize), Folder 3682)
        - Chetro Ketl Ancestral Pueblo, The Great Kiva (No. 3592), 2012 (Box 265 (Oversize), Folder 3683)
        - Chetro Ketl Ancestral Pueblo, The Great Kiva (No. 3594), 2012 (Box 265 (Oversize), Folder 3684)
        - Chetro Ketl Ancestral Pueblo, Kivas - Threatening Rock (No. 3600), 2012 (Box 265 (Oversize), Folder 3685)
        - Chetro Ketl Ancestral Pueblo (No. 3615), 2012 (Box 265 (Oversize), Folder 3686)
        - Chetro Ketl Ancestral Pueblo (No. 3629), 2012 (Box 265 (Oversize), Folder 3687)
        - Chetro Ketl Ancestral Pueblo and Pueblo Bonito (No. 3640), 2012 (Box 265 (Oversize), Folder 3688)
        - Threatening Rock, Pueblo Bonito on left (No. 3649), 2012 (Box 265 (Oversize), Folder 3689)
        - Pueblo Bonito (No. 3674), 2012 (Box 265 (Oversize), Folder 3690)
        - Pueblo Bonito, Kiva (No. 3689), 2012 (Box 265 (Oversize), Folder 3691)
        - Pueblo Bonito (No. 3697), 2012 (Box 265 (Oversize), Folder 3692)
        - Pueblo Bonito (No. 3706), 2012 (Box 265 (Oversize), Folder 3693)
        - Pueblo Bonito (No. 3722), 2012 (Box 265 (Oversize), Folder 3694)
        - Pueblo Bonito (No. 3729), 2012 (Box 265 (Oversize), Folder 3695)
        - Pueblo Bonito (No. 3744), 2012 (Box 265 (Oversize), Folder 3696)
        - Pueblo Bonito (No. 3746), 2012 (Box 265 (Oversize), Folder 3697)
        - Pueblo Bonito (No. 3757), 2012 (Box 265 (Oversize), Folder 3698)
      - El Morro National Monument, New Mexico
        - Inscription Rock (No. 4677), 2013 (Box 266 (Oversize), Folder 3699)
        - Inscription Rock - "T.H. O'Sullivan 1873" (No. 4712), 2013 (Box 266 (Oversize), Folder 3700)
        - Inscription Rock, Steel Bolts in cracl measures gap for expansion or contraction (No. 4721), 2013 (Box 266 (Oversize), Folder 3701)
        - Inscription Rock (No. 4731), 2013 (Box 266 (Oversize), Folder 3702)
        - Inscription Rock (No. 4733), 2013 (Box 266 (Oversize), Folder 3703)
        - Inscription Rock (No. 4765), 2013 (Box 266 (Oversize), Folder 3704)
        - Inscription Rock (No. 4704, 4708, 4709, 4730), 2013 (Box 266 (Oversize), Folder 3705)
          Four discrete images with a manuscript title by the photographer.
      - Painted Desert, New Mexico
        - Painted Desert Inn, Kachina Point - Flag Half Mast, 19 Firefighters perished [at] Yarnell Fire, Arizona (No. 4777), 2013 (Box 266 (Oversize), Folder 3706)
        - Kachina Point, Lihtodendron Wash (No. 4781), 2013 (Box 266 (Oversize), Folder 3707)
        - Chinde Point, Lihtodendron Wash (No. 4783), 2013 (Box 266 (Oversize), Folder 3708)
        - Nizhoni Point (No. 4791), 2013 (Box 266 (Oversize), Folder 3709)
        - Whipple Point (No. 4800), 2013 (Box 266 (Oversize), Folder 3710)
        - Puerco Pueblo (No. 4821), 2013 (Box 266 (Oversize), Folder 3711)
        - Puerco River Dry Wash, Santa Fe Railroad, background (No. 4832), 2013 (Box 266 (Oversize), Folder 3712)
        - Anasazi Ruins, Puerco Pueblo, Newspaper Rock Petroglyphs (No. 4836, 4812, 4835), 2013 (Box 266 (Oversize), Folder 3713)
          Three discrete images.
      - Petrified Forest, Arizona
        - The Teepees (No. 4858), 2013 (Box 267 (Oversize), Folder 3714)
        - The Teepees (No. 4868), 2013 (Box 267 (Oversize), Folder 3715)
        - Blue Mesa (No. 4873), 2013 (Box 267 (Oversize), Folder 3716)
        - Blue Mesa, Puerco River Dry Wash (No. 4876), 2013 (Box 267 (Oversize), Folder 3717)
        - Blue Mesa (No. 4884), 2013 (Box 267 (Oversize), Folder 3718)
        - Blue Mesa (No. 4885), 2013 (Box 267 (Oversize), Folder 3719)
        - Blue Mesa (No. 4892), 2013 (Box 267 (Oversize), Folder 3720)
        - Blue Mesa (No. 4896), 2013 (Box 267 (Oversize), Folder 3721)
        - Blue Mesa, Petrified Wood (No. 4899), 2013 (Box 267 (Oversize), Folder 3722)
        - Blue Mesa, Petrified Wood (No. 4905), 2013 (Box 267 (Oversize), Folder 3723)
        - Agate Bridge (No. 4914), 2013 (Box 267 (Oversize), Folder 3724)
        - Jasper Forest (No. 4928), 2013 (Box 267 (Oversize), Folder 3725)
        - Jasper Forest (No. 4935), 2013 (Box 267 (Oversize), Folder 3726)
        - Jasper Forest (No. 4956), 2013 (Box 267 (Oversize), Folder 3727)
      - Anasazi Ruins - Pueblo of Wupatki, Arizona
        Photographs of Wupatki National Monument.
        - Wukiki (No. 5010), 2013 (Box 267 (Oversize), Folder 3728)
          View of the Wukoki Pueblo
        - Wukiki (No. 5020), 2013 (Box 267 (Oversize), Folder 3729)
        - Wukiki (No. 5028), 2013 (Box 267 (Oversize), Folder 3730)
        - Wukiki (No. 5031), 2013 (Box 267 (Oversize), Folder 3731)
        - Untitled (No. 5032), 2013 (Box 267 (Oversize), Folder 3732)
        - Kivas, foreground and right (No. 5033), 2013 (Box 267 (Oversize), Folder 3733)
        - Untitled (No. 5059), 2013 (Box 267 (Oversize), Folder 3734)
      - Walnut Canyon, Arizona
        - Untitled (No. 5074), 2013 (Box 267 (Oversize), Folder 3735)
        - Untitled (No. 5088), 2013 (Box 267 (Oversize), Folder 3736)
      - Sunset Crater, Arizona
        - Bontino Lava Flow, Mount Eden, background (No. 4971), 2013 (Box 268 (Oversize), Folder 3737)
        - Bontino Lava Flow (No. 4972), 2013 (Box 268 (Oversize), Folder 3738)
        - Cinder Hills (No. 4974), 2013 (Box 268 (Oversize), Folder 3739)
        - Cinder Hills (No. 4994), 2013 (Box 268 (Oversize), Folder 3740)
        - Cinder Hills (No. 4998), 2013 (Box 268 (Oversize), Folder 3741)
        - Sunset Crater Volcano (No. 5002), 2013 (Box 268 (Oversize), Folder 3742)
      - Meteor Crater, also known as Barringer Crater, Arizona
        - Untitled (No. 5110), 2013 (Box 268 (Oversize), Folder 3743)
        - Untitled (No. 5126), 2013 (Box 268 (Oversize), Folder 3744)
        - Untitled (No. 5127), 2013 (Box 268 (Oversize), Folder 3745)
        - Old Mineshaft bottom of Crater (No. 5128), 2013 (Box 268 (Oversize), Folder 3746)
        - Old Mineshaft bottom of Crater (No. 5137), 2013 (Box 268 (Oversize), Folder 3747)
        - Interleaving sheets
    - Reference Inkjet Prints, 8.5 inches by 11 inches
      Organized under two headings: Portrait of Tucker and Photographs in Arizona and New Mexico by Others.
      - Portrait of Tucker
        - Toba Pato Tucker, Photographing, Four Corners, New Mexico, 2010 (Box 269, Folder 3748)
      - Photographs in Arizona and New Mexico by Others
        Arranged by the Tucker under four headings: Canyon de Chelly, Arizona; Grand Canyon, Arizona; Anasazi Ruins - Chaco Canyon, New Mexico; and El Morro National Monument, New Mexico.
        - Canyon de Chelly, Arizona
          - Ancient Ruins in the Cañon de Chelle, New Mexico (No. 10), printed 2013; image created 1873 (Box 269, Folder 3749)
            Photograph by Timothy H. O'Sullivan. Original print in Geographical Surveys West of the 100th Meridian, Photographs Showing Landscapes, Geological and Other Features, Call number WA Photos Folio 55. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 3017, 3021, and 3022.
          - Cañon de Chelle (No. 10), printed 2013; image created 1873 (Box 269, Folder 3750)
            Photograph by Timothy H. O'Sullivan. Original print in Geographical Surveys West of the 100th Meridian, Photographs Showing Landscapes, Geological and Other Features, Call number WA Photos Folio 55. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 2896 to 3121.
          - Ruins of Cliff Dwellings, Canon de Chelly, printed 2013; image created circa 1879-1881 (Box 269, Folder 3751)
            Photograph by John K. Hillers. Original halftone in Frederick Samuel Dellenbaugh Collection of Photographs and Drawings of the Colorado River Region, Call number WA Photos 271. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 3017, 3021, and 3022.
          - Ruins of the De Chelle, Arizona (No. 3705), printed 2013; image created circa 1875-1880 (Box 269, Folder 3752)
            Photograph by William Henry Jackson. From a digital surrogate in the Palace of the Governors Photo Archive, New Mexico History Museum, Santa Fe. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 3017, 3021, and 3022.
          - East Fork, Canyon de Chelly, Arizona, printed 2013; image created circa 1880-1882 (Box 269, Folder 3753)
            Photograph by John K. Hillers. From a digital surrogate in the Palace of the Governors Photo Archive, New Mexico History Museum, Santa Fe. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 2896-3121.
          - Hand Rock, Canyon de Chelly, Arizona, printed 2013; image created circa 1880-1882 (Box 269, Folder 3754)
          - View of Canyon de Chelly, Arizona, printed 2013; image created circa 1880-1882 (Box 269, Folder 3755)
          - Captains of the Canon, Canyon de Chelly, Arizona, printed 2013; image created circa 1879-1880 (Box 269, Folder 3756)
        - Grand Canyon, Arizona
          - Crossing of the Colorado River near mouth of Paria Creek (Plate No. VIII), printed 2013; image created 1873 (Box 269, Folder 3757)
            Lithographic print after a sketch by Gilbert Thompson. Published in Report Upon United States Geographical Surveys West of the One Hundredth Meridian in Charge of First Lieut. Geo. M. Wheeler ... Vol. 1. Geographical report (Washington, Government Print Office, 1875). Call number WA Prints 169. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 3129-3464.
          - Grand Canon of the Colorado, near Paria Creek, Looking East (Plate No. XXIII), printed 2013; image created 1872 (Box 269, Folder 3758)
            Lithographic print after a photograph by William Bell. Published in Report Upon United States Geographical Surveys West of the One Hundredth Meridian in Charge of First Lieut. Geo. M. Wheeler ... Vol. 1. Geographical report (Washington, Government Print Office, 1875). Call number WA Prints 183. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 3129-3464.
          - Powell Monument, printed 2013; image created 1922 February (Box 269, Folder 3759)
            Photograph of the John Wesley Powell Memorial Monument on the South Rim of the Grand Canyon by Mr. Colin of Pasadena, California. Original print in Frederick Samuel Dellenbaugh Collection of Photographs and Drawings of the Colorado River Region, Call number WA Photos 271. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 3258.
          - View of Grand Canyon from Bright Angel Point, Kaibab Forest, Arizona, printed 2013; image created circa 1933 (Box 269, Folder 3760)
            Photographic postcard published by Frasher's, Inc., Pomona, California, and sent by Clarissa Campton Dryden to Frederick Samuel Dellenbaugh, August 10, 1933. Original postacrd in Frederick Samuel Dellenbaugh Collection of Photographs and Drawings of the Colorado River Region, Call number WA Photos 271. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 3129-3464
          - Monument erected to the memory of Major John Wesley Powell. Grand Canyon, Arizona (No. H-1426), printed 2013; image created circa 1916 (Box 269, Folder 3761)
            Photographic postcard published by Fred Harvey, and sent to Harriet Rogers Otis Dellenbaugh, December 28, 1916. Original postcard in Frederick Samuel Dellenbaugh Collection of Photographs and Drawings of the Colorado River Region, Call number WA Photos 271. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 3258.
          - Grand Canyon North Side Near Uinkaret Mountains, printed 2013; image created circa 1871-1878 (Box 269, Folder 3762)
            Photograph by John K. Hillers. Also known as Grand Canyon, looking east from Toroweap. Grand Canyon is a little distance above. Original print in Frederick Samuel Dellenbaugh Collection of Photographs and Drawings of the Colorado River Region, Call number WA Photos 271. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 3129-3464.
          - The Grand Canyon of Arizona, printed 2013; image created circa 1871-1878 (Box 269, Folder 3763)
            Halftone print after a photograph by John K. Hillers. Original print in Frederick Samuel Dellenbaugh Collection of Photographs and Drawings of the Colorado River Region, Call number WA Photos 271. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 3129-3464.
          - From near head of Bright Angel Canyon - almost exactly the same as my sketch - frontispiece of "A Canyon Voyage", printed 2013; image created circa 1910-1930 (Box 269, Folder 3764)
            Photograph by W.I. Starr, title by Frederick Samuel Dellenbaugh. Original print in Frederick Samuel Dellenbaugh Collection of Photographs and Drawings of the Colorado River Region, Call number WA Photos 271. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 3129-3464.
          - Grand Cañon of the Colorado, near Paria Creek, looking West (No. 30), printed 2013; image created 1873 (Box 269, Folder 3765)
            Photograph by William Bell. Original print in Geographical Surveys West of the 100th Meridian, Photographs of Arizona, Nevada, and Utah, Call number WA Photos Folio 56. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 3129-3464.
          - View Looking south into the Grand Cañon of the Colorado, from Sheavwitz Crossing (Plate No. XXI), printed 2013; image created 1872 (Box 269, Folder 3766)
            Lithographic print after a photograph by William Bell. Published in Report Upon United States Geographical Surveys West of the One Hundredth Meridian in Charge of First Lieut. Geo. M. Wheeler ... Vol. 1. Geographical report (Washington, Government Print Office, 1875). Call number WA Prints 181. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 3129-3464.
          - View Looking south into the Grand Cañon of the Colorado, near mouth of the Kanab Wash, looking east (Plate No. XXI), printed 2013; image created 1872 (Box 269, Folder 3767)
            Lithographic print after a photograph probably by William Bell. Published in Report Upon United States Geographical Surveys West of the One Hundredth Meridian in Charge of First Lieut. Geo. M. Wheeler ... Vol. 1. Geographical report (Washington, Government Print Office, 1875). Call number WA Prints 182. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 3129-3464.
          - The Grand Canyon. From top of Granite, South Side near Bright Angel Trail (No. 2252), printed 2013; image created circa 1871-1908 (Box 269, Folder 3768)
            Title from reproduced of image in Frederick Samuel Dellenbaugh, A Canyon Voyage (New York: G.P. Putnam's Sons, 1908) and number from inscription in negative. Print in Frederick Samuel Dellenbaugh Collection of Photographs and Drawings of the Colorado River Region, Call number WA Photos 271. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 3129-3464.
          - Grand Canon of the Colorado (No. 5009), printed 2013; image created circa 1879-1880 (Box 269, Folder 3769)
            From a digital surrogate in the Palace of the Governors Photo Archive, New Mexico History Museum, Santa Fe. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 2896-3121.
          - John Wesley Powell Memorial (No. 3258), 2012 (Box 269, Folder 3770)
            Photograph by Tucker.
        - Anasazi Ruins - Chaco Canyon, New Mexico
          - North Wall of Pueblo Bonito, printed 2013; image created 1901 October 25-26 (Box 269, Folder 3771)
            Photograph by Charles Fletcher Lummis. Man in image is Alfred M. (Alfred Marston) Tozzer. Published in Charles F. Lummis, "A Week of Wonders, II" Land of Sunshine, Volume 15, Number 6 (December 1901): 425-437. From a digital surrogate in the Palace of the Governors Photo Archive, New Mexico History Museum, Santa Fe. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 3722.
          - Pueblo Bonito, Detail, printed 2013; image created 1901 October 25-26 (Box 269, Folder 3772)
            Photograph by Charles Fletcher Lummis. Man in image is Alfred M. (Alfred Marston) Tozzer. From a digital surrogate in the Palace of the Governors Photo Archive, New Mexico History Museum, Santa Fe. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 3722.
          - Pueblo Bonito, printed 2013; image created 1901 October 25-26 (Box 269, Folder 3773)